itsannatopping@gmail.com 603-533-0908

Anna Topping

Hardworking, responsible **Senior Support Engineer** with five years of client and project management experience. Enjoys collaborating with others and enabling teams to reach their highest potential. Seeking opportunity to become an expert in a new platform and have impact through collaboration, teaching and problem solving.

Experience

Ungork I New York, NY

Senior Support Engineer I July 2021 - Present

I serve as the highest escalation point for technical support issues within the Global Support Services team. I maintain a full working knowledge of Unqork's configuration best practices, new features, and platform capabilities. I act as an individual contributor through my independent work on improving our onboarding and monitoring process. I am also building my management toolkit to become a stronger people manager.

Configuration Support Engineer | January 2021 - July 2021

I work closely with engineers, client partners, and delivery team to support Unqork built applications through the SDLC cycle. I am an expert in Unqork configuration through both my own research as well as hands on experience creating Unqork built tools for internal and external use. I share my knowledge with my teammates and those outside of the team who seek our guidance

Associate Support Engineer I April 2020 - January 2021

I use my exceptional problem solving and strong interpersonal communication skills to work with customers and to help resolve their complex Unqork problems.

Zero-In I New York, NY

Web Project Manager I January 2020 - April 2020

I work directly with developers to create new digital marketing solutions and manage API connections to business management softwares like MindBody, as well as integrations with social media platforms like Instagram, and Facebook. I manage the entire life of multiple high-profile web-based projects by communicating with clients, designers, and front end developers.

Digital Account Manager I September 2018 - December 2019

Manager of 73 mid-size accounts, I lead weekly project-update meetings, assess new content requests, and placate support issues and installation requests. I am an account manager as much as I am a project manager, overseeing the workflow for multiple projects at a time by organizing requirements, timelines, and scope. I work directly with clients to onboard users to CMS systems and provide excellent customer service with frequent reach outs and check-in video calls.

Education

General Assembly I New York, NY

Javascript Development I Jan 2020 - April 2020

Mastered the fundamentals of JavaScript and advanced APIs to build a full-functional mobile application.

Emmanuel College I Boston, MA I Class of 2017

Bachelor of Arts in English, Communications, and Media Studies. I GPA: 3.5

- Weekly volunteer with the Urban Food Project and Rosie's Place, 2016 Summer Community Service Fellow with Emmanuel's Food Project.
- · Completed 3 internships with local businesses including WGBH's Direct Marketing Department.

Javascript and · Amazon Web MySQL System · Attention to Skills jQuery Services Management detail Datadog Linux Cloud · A logical Strong • MongoDB Computing approach to communication · Testing and Database work JIRA and AGILE debugging Confident technical trainer